<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="skin.nereus" version="0.0.3" name="Nereus" provider-name="ge2301">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.14.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1440" aspect="4:3" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1280" aspect="3:2" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1200" aspect="16:10" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2040" height="1080" aspect="17:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2560" height="1080" aspect="21:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2338" height="1080" aspect="19.5:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
		<res width="2160" height="1080" aspect="18:9" default="false" folder="xml" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="af_ZA">Nereus oortreksel deur ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Nereus облик от ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Aparença Nereus per ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Vzhled Nereus od autora ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Nereus skin af ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Nereus Skin von ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Το κέλυφος Nereus από τον ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Nereus skin by ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Nereus skin by ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Nereus skin by ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Skin Nereus por ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Skin Nereus, creado por ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="es_MX">Nereus skin por ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="et_EE">Nereus rüü autorilt ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="eu_ES">Nereus azala ge2301 egina.</summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">Nereus on ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage Nereus par ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Nereus, un habillage par ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Pel Nereus por ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">מעטפת Nereus של ge2301</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Nereus presvlaka autora ge2301</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Nereus felszín. Készítette ge2301</summary>
		<summary lang="is_IS">Nereus-skinnið eftir ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Skin Nereus da ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="ja_JP">Nereusスキン by ge2301</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">ge2301가 만든 Nereus 스킨.</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Nereus teminė išvaizda, kurią sukūrė ge2301. </summary>
		<summary lang="lv_LV">Nereus apvalks no ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="mk_MK">Nereus skin by ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="ms_MY">Kulit Nereus oleh ge2301 dan rakan-rakan.</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Esturay-drakt av ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Nereus skin door ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Skóra Eustary autorstwa ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Skin Nereus por ge2301 .</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Visual Nereus de ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Tema Nereus de ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Обложка Nereus. Авторы: ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="sk_SK">Vzhľad Nereus, vytvorili ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS">Маска Nereus аутора ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="sr_RS@latin">Maska Nereus autora ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Nereus, ett skal av ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="szl">Skōra Nereus ôd ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="th_TH">สกิน Nereus โดย ge2301</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Nereus dış görünümü. ge2301</summary>
		<summary lang="uk_UA">Обкладинка Nereus від ge2301.</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">ge2301 开发的 Nereus 皮肤。</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_TW">ge2301與 製作的Nereus佈景主題</summary>
		<description lang="af_ZA">Nereus is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi 17.0 en op. Dit poog om maklik te wees vir eerste keer Kodi gebruikers om te verstaan en te gebruik.</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Nereus е стандартният облик на Kodi 17 и по-новите версии. Целта е да се улеснят хората, които се сблъскват за първи път с Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Nereus és l'aparença predeterminada de Kodi 17.0 i posteriors. Per als usuaris per primera vegada de Kodi, intenta ser fàcil d'entendre i d'utilitzar.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Nereus je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi 17.0 a vyšší. Snaží se být jednoduše pochopitelný a použitelný pro nové uživatele Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="da_DK">Nereus er standardbrugerfladen for Kodi 17.0 og højere. Det forenkler førstegangsbrugen af Kodi ved at gøre det nemmere at forstå og bruge.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Nereus ist der Standardskin für Kodi 17.0 und höher. Ziel war es, einen einfach zu bedienenden Skin für neue Kodi-Benutzer zu entwickeln.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Το Nereus είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για τις εκδόσεις Kodi 17.0 και άνω. Επιχειρεί να είναι προσιτό στους αρχάριους χρήστες του Kodi για να το κατανοήσουν και να το χρησιμοποιήσουν.</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Nereus is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Nereus is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Nereus is the default skin for Kodi 17.0 and above. It attempts to be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use.</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Nereus es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y posteriores. Intenta ser fácil de entender y utilizar para los usuarios Kodi primerizos.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Nereus es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 o superior. Su objetivo es la facilidad de comprensión y uso para usuarios primerizos de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="es_MX">Nereus es el skin por defecto para Kodi 17.0 y superior. Intenta ser fácil para los usuarios de Kodi de primera vez para entender y usar.</description>
		<description lang="eu_ES">Nereus azala kodi 17.0 eta berriagoen azal lehenetsia da. Kodiren erabiltzaile hasiberrientzako erabilerraza eta ulerterraza izaten saiatzen da.</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Nereus on oletusulkoasu Kodin versiosta 17.0 lähtien. Se pyrkii olemaan helppo ymmärtää ja käyttää Kodin ensikäyttäjille. </description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Nereus est l’habillage par défaut pour Kodi 17.0 et ultérieure. Il s’efforce d’être facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs débutants de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Nereus est l'habillage d'origine pour Kodi 17.0 et supérieur. Il est facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs novices de Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Nereus é a pel predefinida para Kodi 17.0 e superior. Esta tenta ser doada de entender e usar polos usuarios recen chegados a Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">Nereus היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי מגרסאות 17.0 ומעלה. מטרת מעטפת זו היא להיות פשוטה לשימוש ולהכרה ראשונית על ידי משתמשים חדשים.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Nereus je uobičajena presvlaka za Kodi 17.0 i novije inačice. To je pokušaj da se novim korisnicima olakša prvo korištenje i kasnija upotreba Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">Az Nereus az alapértelmezett felszín a 17.0 és újabb Kodi kiadásokban.  Megpróbál könnyen kezelhető és használható lenni, az újonc Kodi felhasználóknak is.</description>
		<description lang="is_IS">Nereus er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi 17.0 og nýrri. Með því á að vera auðvelt fyrir fyrsta-skiptis Kodi-notendur að skilja og nota viðmótið.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Nereus è la skin predefinita di Kodi 17.0 e successivi. Cerca di essere facile da capire e usare per i nuovi utenti di Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="ja_JP">NereusはKodi 17.0およびそれ以上のバージョンで標準のスキンです。ユーザーが初めてKodiに触れる際にわかりやすく使えるようにしてあります。</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">Nereus는 Kodi 17.0이상의 기본 스킨입니다. 처음 Kodi를 접하는 사용자가 쉽게 이해하고 사용할 수 있도록 만들었습니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Nereus yra numatytoji Kodi 17.0 ir aukštesnių versijų teminė išvaizda. Jos tikslas yra būti lengvai perprantama naujiems Kodi vartotojams.</description>
		<description lang="ms_MY">Nereus ialah kulit lalai untuk Kodi 17.0 dan ke atas. Kulit yang mudah digunakan buat pengguna Kodi kali pertama untuk memahami dan menggunakannya.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Nereus er forvalgt drakt til Kodi 17.0 og nyere. Det tar mål av seg å være en enkel drakt for førstegangsbrukere av Kodi, slik at det er til å forstå og kan brukes.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Nereus is de standaardskin voor Kodi 17.0 en hoger. Het tracht eenvoudig te begrijpen en te gebruiken te zijn voor beginnende Kodi-gebruikers.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi dla wersji 17.0 i późniejszych. Jest próbą łatwego wprowadzenia początkujących użytkowników w funkcje Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Nereus é a skin padrão para o Kodi 17.0 e acima. Objetiva ser fácil para usuários que iniciam no Kodi pela primeira vez, facilitando aprendizagem de uso do mesmo.</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">O Nereus é o visual por omissão para o Kodi 17.0 e posteriores. Tenta ser simples para os utilizadores menos experientes do Kodi compreenderem e usarem.</description>
		<description lang="ro_RO">Nereus este tema implicită pentru Kodi 17.0 și versiunile ulterioare. Încearcă să fie ușor de înțeles și folosit pentru utilizatorii care folosesc Kodi pentru prima dată.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Nereus — это стандартная обложка Kodi, начиная с версии 17.0.&#10;Простая и понятная в использовании для новых пользователей Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="sk_SK">Nereus je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi 17.0 a vyššie. Pokúša sa byť pre prvotných používateľov Kodi jednoduchým na pochopenie a používanie.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS">Nereus је подразумевана маска за Kodi 17.0 и изнад. Покушава да буде једноставан за разумевање и коришћење новим корисницима Kodi-ја.</description>
		<description lang="sr_RS@latin">Nereus je podrazumevana maska za Kodi 17.0 i iznad. Pokušava da bude jednostavan za razumevanje i korišćenje novim korisnicima Kodija.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Nereus är standardskalet för Kodi 17.0 och uppåt. Det är utformat för att vara lättförståeligt och användarvänligt för förstagångsanvändare av Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="szl">Nereus je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi dlŏ wersyje 17.0 i dalszych. Prōbuje być proste dlŏ używŏczōw, dlŏ kerych Kodi je nowe</description>
		<description lang="th_TH">Nereus คือหน้าตาเริ่มต้นของ Kodi 17.0 และสูงกว่า เป็นความพยายามที่จะทำให้ง่ายสำหรับผู้ใช้ Kodi ในครั้งแรก ที่จะเข้าใจและใช้งาน</description>
		<description lang="tr_TR">Nereus Kodi 17.0 ve yukarısı için varsayılan dış görünümdür. İlk kez Kodi kullananlar için anlaşılması ve kullanımı kolaydır.</description>
		<description lang="uk_UA">Nereus є стандартною обкладинкою Kodi 17.0 і подальших версій. Її основна ідея — простота використання для нових користувачів Kodi.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">Nereus 是 Kodi 17.0 的默认皮肤。它力求使首次使用 Kodi 的用户易于上手。</description>
		<description lang="zh_TW">Nereus是Kodi 17.0開始搭載的預設佈景主題。主要在讓第一次使用 Kodi 的使用者可以簡單地上手。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="af_ZA">Nereus is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi, verwydering mag probleme veroorsaak</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="bg_BG">Nereus е стандартният облик на Kodi. Премахването му може да предизвика проблеми</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ca_ES">Nereus és l'aparença predeterminada de Kodi, si s'elimina pot causar problemes.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Nereus je výchozí vzhled pro Kodi, jeho odebrání může způsobit problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cy_GB">Nereus yw croen diofyn Kodi. Efallai bydd ei dynnu yn achosi problemau</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="da_DK">Nereus er standard brugerfladen. Fjernes det kan der opstå problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Nereus ist der Standardskin von Kodi. Ein Entfernen des Skins kann Probleme verursachen.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el_GR">Το Nereus είναι η προεπιλεγμένη αμφίεση για το Kodi. Η αφαίρεσή του μπορεί να δημιουργήσει προβλήματα.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">Nereus is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Nereus is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_US">Nereus is the default skin for Kodi, removing it may cause issues</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_AR">Nereus es el skin por defecto de Kodi. Borrarlo puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_ES">Nereus es el skin por defecto de Kodi. Desinstalarlo puede causar problemas.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_MX">Nereus es el skin por defecto para Kodi, su eliminación puede causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="eu_ES">Nereus Kodiren azal lehenetsia da. Ezabatzeak arazoak eragin ditzake</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fi_FI">Nereus on Kodin oletusulkoasu, sen poisto voi aiheuttaa ongelmia</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Nereus est l’habillage par défaut de Kodi, le supprimer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Nereus est l'habillage d'origine de Kodi, le retirer peut créer des problèmes</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="gl_ES">Nereus é a pel predefinida para Kodi e eliminala pode causar problemas.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="he_IL">Nereus היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של קודי, הסרתה עלולה לגרום לתקלות</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hr_HR">Nereus je uobičajena presvlaka za Kodi, njegovim uklanjanjem može uzrokovati poteškoće</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hu_HU">Az Nereus az alapértelmezett Kodi felszín. Eltávolítása problémákat okozhat.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="is_IS">Nereus er sjálfgefið skinn fyrir Kodi, ef það er fjarlægt gætu komið upp ýmis vandamál</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it_IT">Nereus è la skin predefinita di Kodi, rimuoverla potrebbe causare problemi</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ja_JP">NereusはKodiのデフォルトスキンなので、これを削除するとうまく動かなくなる可能性があります</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ko_KR">Nereus는 Kodi의 기본스킨으로 제거시 문제가 생길 수 있습니다.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Nereus yra numatytoji Kodi teminė išvaizda, jos pašalinimas gali sukelti problemų</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ms_MY">Nereus ialah kulit lalai Kodi, mengubahnya boleh menimbulkan isu.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nb_NO">Nereus er forvalgt drakt for Kodi, dersom du fjerner det kan det forårsake problemer.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Nereus is de standaardskin voor Kodi, het verwijderen van Nereus kan leiden tot problemen.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Eustary jest domyślną skórą Kodi, usunięciejej może powodować problemy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Nereus é a skin padrão para o Kodi, removendo-a pode causar problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_PT">O Nereus é o visual por omissão do Kodi; se o remover, poderá ter alguns problemas</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ro_RO">Nereus este tema implicită pentru Kodi, eliminarea ei poate cauza probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Nereus — это стандартная обложка Kodi, и ее удаление может привести к возникновению проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sk_SK">Nereus je predvolený vzhľad pre Kodi, jeho odstránenie môže spôsobiť problémy</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS">Nereus је подразумевана маска за Kodi, уклањање може изазвати проблеме</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sr_RS@latin">Nereus je podrazumevana maska za Kodi, uklanjanje može izazvati probleme</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Nereus är Kodis standardskal. Om du tar bort det kan det orsaka problem.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="szl">Nereus je wychodnōm skōrōm Kodi, jij uchrōniynie może sprŏwiać niyprzileżytości</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="th_TH">Nereus เป็นหน้าตาเริ่มต้นสำหรับ Kodi, การลบมัน อาจทำให้เกิดปัญหา</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Nereus Kodi için varsayılan dış görünümdür, kaldırmak sorunlara yol açabilir</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="uk_UA">Nereus — основна обкладинка Kodi, і її видалення може призвести до проблем</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_CN">Nereus 是 Kodi 的默认皮肤，删除它可能导致故障。</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_TW">Nereus 是 Kodi 預設的佈景主題，移除它可能會造成問題</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/</forum>
		<source>https://github.com/ge2301/Nereus_Kodi/</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-07.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-08.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>
